我是总统
This is the president.
-让康威接电话  -你要跟我说话
- Put on Conway. - You will speak to me.
不  我们只跟他谈  否则挂断
No, we only talk to him or we hang up.
听到直升机了吗  还有狗吠
Do you hear the helicopters yet? Or the dogs?
我们接近了  很快就能找到你
We're getting closer and we will find you.
唯一的问题是  我们抓到你们之前
The only question is will you work with us
你们是否愿意合作
before we get there?
赎金和撤军都别指望了
The money's not happening and neither is the military withdrawal.
但你够聪明  早就知道
But you're smart enough to know that.
重点在于艾哈迈德
The objective here is Ahmadi,
这是我想谈的
and that's what I'd like to discuss.
选择权在你
Well, the choice is yours.
你要么满足我们的要求  要么不满足
You either meet our demands or you don't.
我昨晚跟康威州长深谈过
I spoke at length last night with Governor Conway.
我今早本想无视你的电话
I was of a mind to ignore your call this morning,
但他说服我继续跟你沟通
but he convinced me that we should keep talking.
是吧  州长
Isn't that right, Governor?
-我只想寻求和平解决方案  -我也是
- I just want a peaceful resolution. - As do I.
你想叫上州长  我想叫上艾哈迈德
You wanted to include the Governor, I want to include Ahmadi.
-你是在拖延  -你不想跟你的领袖说话吗
- You're trying to stall. - You refusing to speak to your leader?
他在线吗
Is he on now?
你释放米勒一家  我们就让他跟你通话
You release the Millers, then we put him on.
不  你无权谈条件
No, you don't get to dictate terms.
你表现出诚意  我们才会还以诚意
We show good will when you show good will.
我给你10秒钟重新考虑
I'm giving you ten seconds to reconsider your position.
之后  我们就切断电话
After that, we disconnect the call.
真主的旨意  我们会杀了他们
Insha'Allah. We'll kill them.
10秒钟  现在开始
Ten seconds, starting now.
5秒钟
Five seconds.
-结束通话  -一个人质
- End the call. - One hostage.
-三个  -一个
- All three. - One.
把女儿和母亲交出来
Give us the daughter and the mother.
不  女孩我们要留下
No, we keep the girl.
你已经两次打通了
You managed to get the president of the United States on the phone
美国总统的电话
not once, but twice.
你得释放女儿和母亲
You will release the daughter and the mother
否则我再也不会与你联络了
or you will never hear from me again,
而且你会失去与你领袖通话的机会
and you will lose your chance to speak to your leader.
马上说
Tell me now.
他们挂线了  先生
They've disconnected, sir.
停下
Stop.
艾哈迈德先生
Mr. Ahmadi.
你可以在楼上洗澡  衣柜里有干净衣服
You can shower upstairs. There's fresh clothes in the closet.
只有参联会主席和护送他的
The only people who know are the Chairman
海豹突击队队员知道
and the SEALs who escorted him.
-通话线路安全吗  -直通总统办公室
- Do we have a secure line? - Direct to the Oval.
总统先生
Mr. President...
换了我绝不会同意把艾哈迈德扯进来
I would have never condoned bringing Ahmadi into this.
幸好  我做决定的依据
Well, lucky for me, I'm not making decisions
不是你会同意什么
based on what you would or would not condone.
等着我告诉媒体你把话强加于我
Watch me tell the press you put words in my mouth.
随意
Feel free.
但我觉得他们不太可能会相信你
I think they'll have a hard time believing you, though.
看看你的信息  你的手下肯定一直在给你发邮件
Check your messages. I'm sure your staff's been emailing you.
安排车送州长和他家人去机场
Arrange for a car to get the governor and his family to the airport.
回纽约一路顺风
Have a safe trip back to New York.
情报委员会成员称  康威撒谎
我叫人送来了午餐
I've had lunch brought in.
你肯定挺久没吃过热乎乎的饭菜了
I'm sure it's been quite a while since you've had a hot meal.
-我不会吃的  -你不饿吗
- I won't be eating it. - Aren't you hungry?
我不想受刑的时候吐出来
I don't wanna get sick while I'm being tortured.
没人会给你用刑  请坐吧
No one's getting tortured. Please, have a seat.
你要我叫这些人放了那家人  是吗
You want me to tell these men to release the family, right?
否则  你就得做你必须做的了
If I don't, you'll do what you have to do.
如果我们是那个意思
Oh, if we had any intention of that,
你就不可能离开关塔那摩
you never would have left Guantanamo.
我也不会来这儿
Nor would I be here.
这是哪里
Where is here?
弗吉尼亚州  政府安全屋
Virginia, in a government safe house.
为什么你来
And why you?
出于尊敬  由于事情重大
Out of respect... for the gravity of this situation.
我觉得你是想羞辱我
I think your intention is to humiliate me.
我给你提供了衣服  食物
You've been properly clothed, offered food.
怎么羞辱你了
How are we humiliating you?
我坐在一个女人对面
I'm sitting across from a woman.
没必要装样子了
There's no reason to keep up the facade.
你和你弟弟不是原教旨主义者
You and your brother are not fundamentalists,
也不是叙利亚人
nor are you Syrian.
那是中情局告诉你的吗
This what the CIA's feeding you?
你是伊拉克人  你真名是阿瓦德
You're Iraqi. Your real name is Al Awad.
其实  这上面说你2000年加入了
Actually, it says that you joined
复兴社会党
the Baath Party in 2000.
你2001年到2002年间是
You were the assistant to the
基建副部长的助理
undersecretary of infrastructure, 2001, 2002.
随你怎么说
Say whatever you want.
我弟弟会否认  你别想说服除你之外的任何人
My brother will deny. You won't convince anyone but yourselves.
我们驱逐了复兴社会党
We expel the Baathists
你就从官僚变成了极端主义者
and you go from a bureaucrat to an extremist.
但你是个受过高等教育的人  尤瑟夫
But you're a well-educated man, Yusuf...
你才不在乎伊斯兰或哈里发
and you don't care about Islam or the caliphate.
你只是在利用那个刺激士兵情绪
You're just using that to radicalize soldiers.
就像你利用民主和自由那样
Just as you use democracy and freedom.
现在我们理解彼此了
So now we understand each other.
尤瑟夫·艾哈迈德仍被单独监禁在关塔那摩监狱
Yusuf Al Ahmadi remains in solitary confinement in Guantanamo.
如果卡洛琳和梅莉莎·米勒获释
If Caroline and Melissa Miller are released,
我们将允许劫持者在监督下与其联络
we will allow supervised contact with the kidnappers.
马克
Mark.
艾哈迈德一向鼓励这样的恐怖行动
Ahmadi has consistently encouraged acts of terror like this one.
你为什么认为任何的对话
What makes you think that any sort of dialogue
能带来和平的结果
will lead to a peaceful resolution?
要么就完全不建立对话
Well, the alternative is no dialogue at all.
我们想用尽一切办法
We don't wanna leave any stone unturned.
莎拉
Sara.
你是否可以就《华尔街电讯报》的文章
Will you comment on the Wall Street Telegraph article
指出康威州长可能干涉了
about Governor Conway's alleged interference
众议院情报委员会做出评论
with the House Intelligence Committee?
它确认了我们早有怀疑的事
Well, it confirms what we suspected to be true,
但我想你需要的是州长的评论  而非我的
but I think you want the governor's comment, not ours.
沃勒克议员在扭曲事实
Congressman Walleck is misrepresenting events.
-你是说他撒谎了  -我是说他所言不实
- You're saying he lied? - I'm saying he misrepresented.
我在情报委员会有多位朋友
I have a number of friends on the Intelligence Committee,
我是否偶尔跟他们谈话  当然
and do I speak with them sometimes? Of course.
但这跟干涉不是一回事
But that's not the same as interfering.
那么你从未跟委员会成员
So you never discussed the Russia plan
谈论过俄国的计划
with anyone on the committee?
我们或许谈论过
We may have discussed it,
但我又没下达命令
but it's not as though I was issuing orders.
而且我得说  大家现在应该首要关注
And I have to say, everyone's primary focus right now
米勒一家  而非此事
needs to be on the Miller family, not this.
总统是否要求你离开白宫
Did the president ask you to leave the White House?
我们都认为我该做的已经做完
Uh, we agreed that I'd done my part,
其他要靠他了
and that the rest is up to him.
能跟我们谈谈昨晚你跟总统
Can you tell us about your conversation last night
关于艾哈迈德的讨论吗
with the president, regarding Ahmadi?
先说到这儿吧  谢谢大家
That'll be all for now. Thank you so much.
问个问题  先生
Question, sir.
走吧
Let's go.
等等  莉莉的车座还没弄好
Uh, hold on, I'm still fastening Lily's car seat.
-威尔  -别说了
- Will-- - Not a word.
我得说  将军对你说
Well, I have to tell you, the general's apeshit
为自己服役感到羞耻暴跳如雷
over what you said about being ashamed of your service.
他可能会接受采访
He may talk to the press.
没想出如何合适地回应这堆狗屁
Nobody does any press until we have a proper response
谁都不许接受采访
to all this shit.
爸爸说了  "狗屁"   狗屁  狗屁
Daddy said "Shit." Shit, shit, shit!
住口
Stop it!
你得给我挖到沃勒克的把柄
You need to bring me something on Walleck.
我们得让他信誉扫地
We need to discredit him.
-弄好了没有  -你不用冲我们撒火
- Are you done yet? - You don't need to snap at us.
-好了没有  -好了
- Are you done yet? - Yes.
快走  马上
Let's go. Now.
那是如果他们获释
That's if they're released.
等我们了解了具体情况会把空白处补上
We'll fill in the blanks once we have details.
这是为最糟糕的情况准备的
This is if the worst happens.
耶茨写的吗
Yates wrote these?
不  我先写了个底
No, I... I took a stab at it first.
另外  汤姆·汉默施密特打来了
Also, Tom Hammerschmidt called.
他想采访总统
He wants an interview with the president.
不肯说是什么事
He wouldn't say what for.
他现在是哪家的
What outlet is he with now?
他回《先驱报》了  说给你发了邮件
He's back at the Herald. Said he emailed you directly.
雷米·丹顿  杰姬·夏普和加勒特·沃克均已公开作证
让我单独待会儿
I need the room.
都出去
Everyone out.
接《先驱报》
Get me the Herald.
汤姆·汉默施密特
Tom Hammerschmidt.
这里有个手机信号塔
Well, there's a cell tower here.
一般流量不多
Uh, typically very low traffic,
但在来电期间有增加
but it showed higher usage during the time of the call,
尤其是东南天线
especially the southeastern antenna.
那么我们应该能定位热点  锁定位置
So we should be able to ping the hotspot, zero in?
信号塔很多
Eh, it's hundreds of tower faces.
我能说出大致区域
I can give you the general area,
具体定位要更久
but pinpointing will take longer.
而且我无法保证肯定是他们
I can't even guarantee it's gonna be them.
分析每一座塔
I want every one of those towers analyzed.
专注分析背景环境噪声会更有收效
Well, we're better off concentrating on ambient background sound.
如果我能把那个跟
If I can match that to other calls made
这一带的其他通话做匹配
in this area around the same time as--
我不是在问你的建议
I'm not asking your advice.
我是告诉你该做什么
I'm telling you what I want you to do.
分析信号塔数据
Focus on the tower data.
我们本来关注的是这里
We were concentrating on this area,
但看来他们更接近这里
but it looks like they're closer to here.
我们安排了地面小队展开了搜查网络
We've got ground teams setting up a search grid.
可以用卫星吗
Can we use satellites?
我们用了  但区域内有数百个
We are, but there are over 100 possible structures
可能建筑
within the zone.
-要逐个搜查  -要多久
- Each one of them needs to be checked. - How long?
如果走运  几小时  要不可能得拖到明天
If we get lucky, within hours. If not, could be tomorrow.
先生  斯坦普先生来了
Sir, Mr. Stamper's here.
-他说是急事  -谢谢
- He says it's urgent. - Thank you.
汤姆·汉默施密特说他们今天就会发布
Hammerschmidt says they go online today,
不管您是否做出评价
whether you comment or not.
出行记录不算铁证
Travel logs are not hard evidence.
这些引言都是间接证据
These quotes are circumstantial.
但加在一起  我不知道我们该怎么解释
But all of it combined... I don't know how we spin this.
有分量很重的人愿公开作证
He's got heavy hitters on the record.
我要放出杰姬和雷米的照片吗
Should I release the photos of Jackie and Remy?
他们把外遇的事告诉他了
They told him about the affair.
他要在文章里写我们威胁要曝光他们
He's putting in the article that we threatened to expose them.
怎么会发生这种事
How did this happen?
你也有责任
This is as much on you.
我可以列出一张他还没找到的人的名单
I can put together a list of the people he hasn't gotten to yet.
让他拿到掩盖的证据吗
And give him proof of a cover-up?
他说得对  如果我们再联络塔斯克或拉尼根
He's right. If we reach out to Tusk or Lanagin--
把汉默施密特叫来
I want Hammerschmidt here.
-先生  我不是说  -尽快安排
- Sir, I wasn't suggesting-- - Set it up as soon as possible.
美国政府绝不会承认哈里发
The U.S. Government will never recognize the caliphate.
当然
No, of course not.
但我们让复兴社会党重回政府
But we can reintegrate the Baathists into the government.
什么政府  伊拉克已经没有政府了
What government? There's no government in Iraq.
伊拉克已经没有了  有巴格达
There is no Iraq. There's Baghdad.
什叶派  逊尼派  库尔德派
Shia, Sunni, Kurd...
叙利亚也是如此
Syria is the same.
我们驱逐你们之前  你们维持了秩序
You maintained order before we shut you out.
我们不能支持神政
Now, we can't support a theocracy,
但我们可以让军队重新掌握控制权
but we can put the military back in control.
我们招募的士兵怎么办
What do we do with all the soldiers we've recruited?
他们不会接受世俗国家
They won't accept a secular government.
你要管好他们
You'll keep them in check.
如果有必要  考武力
With force, if necessary.
冲替我们扛枪的人开枪吗
Use our guns on the men who carried it for us.
那又如何  如果你能重新掌权的话
What does it matter... if you have back your power?
如果你们真这么打算  为什么不公开说
If this is your intention, why have you said nothing publicly?
因为你知道这一切
Because you know that all of this
只能闭门商量
has to be done behind closed doors.
我们得表现得像是我们消灭了哈里发国
We need to give the appearance that we neutralized ICO.
如果他们不释放人质呢
What happens if they don't release the hostages?
那你回古巴
Well, then you go back to Cuba.
如果他们放了人质  我们就让你跟他们通话
If they do, then we put you on the phone with them...
你叫他们把第三名人质也放掉
and you tell them to release the third.
然后你还是会送我回古巴
And then you send me back to Cuba anyway.
我明白你为什么不信任我们
I do understand why you don't trust us,
但另一个选择呢
but what is the alternative?
他们死了  这样我们更有理由
These people die, and then it gives us all the justification we need
全面进攻
for a full offensive.
那得要很多年
That's years...
而且你别想完全消灭我们
and you won't completely destroy us.
不能完全  但也足以让你不值一提
Not completely, but enough to make you irrelevant.
我们也可以悄悄合作
Or we can quietly work together.
哈里发国消亡  你和你的将军大权在握
ICO fades, and you and your generals get control.
-知道克莱尔在哪吗  -不  我们在找她呢
- Do you know where Claire is? - No, we're trying to find her.
她如果要去哪一般会告诉我
She usually keeps me informed if she's going somewhere.
你问过特勤局吗
Have you asked Secret Service?
-他们不知道  -他们肯定知道
- They didn't know. - They have to know.
-我再去问问  -谢谢
- I'll go ask again. - Thanks.
她不在宅邸
She wasn't at the residence.
-你还去了那儿  -十分钟前
- You went up there? - Ten minutes ago.
你俩到底怎么回事
What's going on between you two?
你以为我没发现吗
You think I haven't noticed?
你俩说话的样子  你来得多勤
How you two talk? How often you're here?
我都不能随随便便进出宅邸
I don't even have unrestricted access to the residence.
她母亲死时  我陪在她身边
I was with her when her mother died.
这让我们变得亲近
It made us close.
你不要想太多
Don't read too much into it.
不管你们有多亲近
Well, however close you are,
只要别让外人想太多就好
just make sure that nobody else can read too much into it.
等你见到克莱尔  告诉她我回家了
Well, if you see Claire, tell her I went home.
如果她想找我的话
If she needs me.
不要和他面谈
Don't meet face-to-face.
让他用书面形式把问题传给你
Have him submit the questions in writing.
但如果我见见他  也许能让他先停停
Yeah, but if I meet with him, maybe I can give him pause.
不  他是想诓你露出马脚
No, he's trying to trap you into giving something away.
那绝不可能
That's not going to happen.
-真是挑了个好时候  -你那边如何
- The timing on this-- - How's your end?
就要说通他了
He's getting there.
你集中精力对付他  我对付哈默施密特
Well, you focus on him. I'll handle Hammerschmidt.
你在抽烟吗
Are you smoking?
-你怎么知道  -我能听见
- How did you know? - I can hear it.
如果这报道出来
If this story comes out,
害死我们的不会是烟
it won't be the smoking that does us in.
他们被杀了吗
Have they been killed?
你好像不高兴
You look upset.
你想你妻子吗
Do you miss your wife?
你才不在乎我妻子
You don't care about my wife.
你们夫妻俩我都不在乎
Ah, I don't care about either of you...
你们或是你们的孩子是死是活  我都不在乎
whether you live or die... or your children do.
但如果每月让你和家人通一次话能说通你
But if speaking to your family once a month will get us there,
我会考虑的
I'll put that on the table.
我已经三年没见过我妻子了
I haven't seen my wife in three years.
我从来没见过我儿子  我女儿根本不记得我
I have a son I've never met, a daughter that doesn't remember me.
这是我们选择的路
This is our path.
哪怕他们被杀吗
Even if they're killed?
是的
Yes.
他们会被杀的
Because they will be.
我不惜一死  他们也是一样
I'm willing to die, and so are they.
-这是他们的选择吗  -什么选择
- Would they have made that choice? - What choice?
他们只知道你们的炸弹
All they've known are your bombs.
一弹下来  人没了
Poof, gone.
我们的厉害之处
We're effective
就在于我们让你们感受到了那痛苦
because we make you feel the pain.
而我们一生都在承受这种痛苦
We've felt it all our lives.
进
Yes?
-汤姆  -总统先生
- Tom. - Mr. President.
我得说明白  今天我们的谈话不能公开
I'm gonna ask that everything we discuss today is off the record.
-明白  -上次我们见面的时候
- Understood. - Now, the last time we met,
是在副总统的办公室
it was in the vice president's office,
你指控我靠操纵马修斯当上了副总统
and you claim that I acquired that office by manipulating Matthews.
指控你的不是我  是沃克总统
I don't claim that. President Walker does.
是啊  那个自尝苦果心怀怨愤的男人
Oh, yes. A man made bitter by his own mistakes.
你还声称是我阴谋赶走了他
And you also claim that I then acquired this office
坐上了总统之位
by pushing out that very same man.
-丹顿和夏普证实了此事  -是吗
- Danton and Sharp corroborated. - Oh, yes.
这两个人和我有很深的宿怨
Two people with very big chips on their shoulders,
无非是想给他们的出轨编个借口罢了
fabricating all this nonsense to justify their infidelity.
你是说你没胁迫过他们
You're saying you didn't blackmail them?
我曾对许多人施压  汤姆
I pressure a lot of people, Tom.
这是政治的一部分
That's part of politics.
但从没威胁过他们
But never those two.
丹顿的父母说
Danton's parents say
莉安·哈维拜访过他们在迈阿密的家
LeAnn Harvey came to their house in Miami.
那应该是他想拉拢莉安支持他的俄国计划
Well, I imagine that's because he wanted LeAnn on the Russian plan.
那为什么是她上门  而不是他去找她
Then why did she come to him instead of him coming to her?
我不跟你扯什么有的没的
Look, I'm not gonna get into the weeds on this,
我就跟你直说了吧
but let's just cut to the chase.
你现在提出的这些指控
The allegations that you're making
就和你第一次见我时所说的一样都是胡扯
are just as ludicrous as they were the first time we met.
我当时没什么确实证据  这回我有了
I had nothing concrete then. This time I do.
就光那三个急于报复我的人
Three people with an ax to grind,
出行记录  连点干货都没有吗
no hard evidence and some travel logs?
这算什么"确实"证据
I'd hardly call that concrete.
写报道已经够看了
It's enough for a story.
你这简直是凭空捏造
You're floating an idea out of thin air.
让我戳穿你的真实意图吧  你就是想趁大选
Let's just call this what it is: blatant sensationalism
-搞个大新闻哗众取宠  -我没有捏造
- tied to the election-- - I don't float.
...哗众取宠来提升你们的发行量
Tied to an election to boost your circulation
因为《先驱报》的读者在大量流失
because the Herald is losing readership.
先生  我绝不会捏造故事试探风向
Sir, I don't float stories to see if they're seaworthy,
我对发行量更是毫不在乎
and I don't give a shit about circulation.
我现在只关注真相
The only thing I care about is the truth.
真相  所以你联系雷蒙德·塔斯克
The truth? So have you reached out to Raymond Tusk
要他评论了吗  或是丹尼尔·拉尼根
for a comment? Or Daniel Lanagin?
我可没看见他们的言论
I don't see their quotes in here.
如果你真的要查真相
I mean, if you're going for the truth,
难道不该查得全面一点  公正一点吗
doesn't that include being thorough? Being balanced?
所以我才想给你机会就此事发表评论
Which is why I'm giving you an opportunity to comment.
那有没有国会的议员
And what about any members of Congress?
我也没看见他们的话
I don't see their quotes in here.
相信等文章发布  他们会接我的电话的
I'm sure they'll answer my calls once this article comes out.
我看你压根不敢打给他们
Oh, I think you're afraid to make those calls,
因为你知道他们会看穿报道的实质
'cause you know they'll see this for what it is...
全无根据的小报八卦
unsupported tabloid gossip.
助理党鞭  你的前幕僚长
The assistant whip, your former Chief of Staff,
外加一位美国前总统
an ex-president of the United States.
这可不是八卦  这是新闻
That's not gossip. It's news.
司法部肯定会展开听证调查的
There's no way the Justice Department doesn't open up an inquiry.
就算司法部无视  国会共和党团也不会放过
And if they don't, the Republicans in Congress will.
随你贬低我  但你知道这事会是什么结果
Downplay this all you want, but you know where this story leads.
我知道这是怎么回事
I know what this story is.
政治陷害  就这么简单
Political sabotage, plain and simple.
玛格丽特·蒂尔顿当年没这么下作  汤姆
Margaret Tilden used to have some integrity, Tom.
你也是
And so did you.
你为什么要浪费全国人民的时间
Why are you wasting America's time with this,
非挑眼下这个危急关头
in the middle of this crisis?
你的良心哪去了
Where is your conscience?
我也想问你这个问题
That's the question I want you to answer.
什么事
Yes?
先生  他们把母女俩的地址发过来了
Sir, they emailed a location of the mother and daughter.
麻烦把汉默施密特先生带到罗斯福室去
Will you please show Mr. Hammerschmidt into the Roosevelt Room?
不用了  我这就走
There's no need. I'll be going.
那可不行  咱俩话还没说完呢  汤姆
Oh, no, no, no. You and I are not done, Tom.
卡洛琳和梅莉沙·米勒于东部时间
Caroline and Melissa Miller were rescued
12:30左右被联调局外勤探员寻获
at approximately 12:30 Eastern Standard Time by FBI field agents.
除了绑架造成的精神创伤之外
Aside from the psychological trauma of their ordeal,
两人健康状况良好
both are unharmed and healthy.
我马上会联系她们  她们接受体检后
I'll be calling them soon, and I hope to meet them soon,
我希望能尽快见到她们
once they have had their full medical examinations.
卡洛琳和梅莉莎·米勒获救
虽然我对母女二人平安感到宽慰
And while I am greatly relieved to have them both safe,
但詹姆斯·米勒仍处境危险
James Miller remains in danger.
我将拼尽全力  争取再次在这个讲台上
And we will not rest until I can come to this podium
发布这样的好消息
and make another announcement like this one,
向各位通报他的平安
informing you of his safe return.
格雷森先生将继续回答各位的问题
Mr. Grayson will answer any questions you may have.
我得回去主持营救了  谢谢各位
I must get back to work. Thank you all very much.
他们还活着  多少有你点功劳
They're alive. You can take some credit for that.
安德伍德肯定正把她们接去白宫
I'm sure Underwood's flying them to the White House right now.
人人都会记住这个镜头
That's the image everyone will remember.
热烈的拥抱  安抚的话语
The warm embrace, the reassuring words.
他一点功劳都不会分给我的
I mean, he's not gonna let me take one ounce of credit for this.
詹姆斯·米勒搜救工作仍在进行
如果她们愿意见媒体的话
If they choose to talk with the media, however,
我们肯定会进行安排
we will certainly facilitate that.
现在请各位提问
I will now take some of your questions.
如果我和莉莉被绑了呢
What if it were Lily and me?
威尔  如果是我和莉莉被绑架了呢
Will, what if it were me and Lily?
你也会这么考虑吗
Would this be your thinking?
-"政治影响"  -别  汉娜
- "The political fallout"? - Don't, Hannah.
别突然变软弱了
Don't get weak on me.
我可以确认我们的重点搜索区域在这里
I can confirm that that is an area where our focus is,
但我只能说到这一步了
but that's about as much detail as I can go into.
绑匪和你们联系了吗
Have the kidnappers made contact?
如果联系了
And if so,
你们让他们和艾哈迈德对话了吗
did you put them in touch with Ahmadi?
他们尚未联系我们  我们敦促他们尽快联系
They have not made contact. We encourage them to do so.
而且我方的提议仍然有效
And, yes, the offer still stands.
-玛丽  -你们凭什么确信
- Mary. - Uh, what assurances do you have
艾哈迈德会照你们的要求进行对话
that Ahmadi will say what you want him to?
我们不能确信  也不能强迫他
We don't, and we can't force him to.
但我们希望他能和我们合作
But we're hoping that he will work with us on this.
古巴那边是谁负责监督他进行通话
Who's managing the call from his side in Cuba?
抱歉  我不能透露
I'm sorry, I can't go into details on that.
虽然母女俩都被蒙了眼
Both were blindfolded in the car,
但母亲估计他们开了45分钟的车
but the mother estimates a drive time of 45 minutes.
这就使搜索范围缩小到六栋建筑
That narrows the search to six structures.
也许他们已经逃跑了
Unless they're on the move.
如果他们穿过了路卡
If they're past the roadblocks already,
那他们也得停下来打电话
they've gotta stop somewhere to make the call.
我们追踪电话取得了进展
And we've had some progress on tracing the call.
你们把我的算法都拿去了
You're taking my algorithms.
我们需要更多人手  而这里又坐不下
We need more teams on this. There is not enough room here.
你知道我接到命令
You know my instructions were never
任何东西都不能离开这栋楼
to let anything leave this building.
而我们有局长的直接命令
We have an order from the director.
如果你们让更多人搀和进来会造成混乱的
Well, if you put more teams on this, it'll cause confusion.
回家吧  麦卡伦先生  你在这儿熬两天了
Go home, Mr. Macallan. You've been here for two days straight.
我绝不会把这事交给
I am not leaving this in the hands of people
不清楚情况的人
who do not know what they're doing.
我们已经安排好了
We've got it covered.
回家休息吧  需要的话会联系你的
Go home. Get some rest. We'll let you know if we need you.
这两个小子并不想杀人
These boys don't wanna kill anyone.
否则  就不会释放两名人质
If they did, they wouldn't have released two hostages.
他们其实是在找台阶下
They're actually looking for an excuse to back out.
如果对话片段上了电视  我就成了叛徒
If the media plays that video, I look like a traitor.
我们告诉他们这是前提条件
We tell them it's a precondition.
要是他们敢泄露  协议就取消
If they share it, the deal is off.
我怎么知道你不会泄露呢
How do I know you won't?
我不能逼你相信我
I can't force you to believe me...
但我们只需几小时就能找到他们
but we are hours from finding them.
你知道规矩
And you know how this goes.
要是吉姆·米勒死了  他们也会死
Jim Miller dies. They die.
你回到古巴  我们就开战
You go back to Cuba. We go to war.
我们已经在交战了
We're already at war.
尤瑟夫  你有一次
Yusuf, you have one chance
改变家乡情况的机会
to change the conditions at home.
你浪费机会  就毁了你为之奋斗过的一切
You squander it, you destroy everything you have ever fought for.
你知道奋斗的滋味吗
What do you know about fighting for anything?
我们说完了  把他押回去
We're done here. Send him back.
好吧
All right.
我照你说的做
I'll do what you ask.
给他穿上囚服  我们在地下室拍
Put him back in his jumpsuit. We'll film in the basement.
是  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
告诉参议员  我回来就给他打电话
Tell the senator I'll call him when I get back.
-总统先生  -凯茜
- Mr. President. -Oh, Cathy.
我知道我们都没机会讨论这一切
I realize we haven't had a chance to discuss everything.
等到把人质救出来
We'll talk foreign policy consequences
我们就讨论外交政策的后果
once we've resolved this hostage situation.
不是那事  《先驱报》联系我了
It's not that. The Herald contacted me.
一名记者打给我的办公室  我读过邮件了
A reporter called my office. I've read the email.
-你没给他们回电  -当然没
- You didn't call them back? - 'Course not.
好  什么都别做也别说  我来处理
All right. Don't do or say anything. I'll handle it.
-怎么处理  -我还不知道
- How? - I don't know yet.
沃克说我们同谋拿下了国务卿之位
Walker says we conspired for Secretary of State,
还说我在调查中庇护他
and saying I gave him asylum during the investigation.
要是他们出版这些  我也会被活剥
If they publish this, I get skinned alive, too.
我们会没事的  凯茜  相信我
We're going to be all right, Cathy. Trust me on this.
我刚和国务卿杜兰特谈过
I just spoke with Secretary Durant.
我们定好了时间
We have a timeline.
同事们要是没我的消息
My folks don't hear from me,
就开始在整点打电话
they start making calls on the hour.
先打给杜兰特
Durant was first.
再打给博奇
Birch is next.
然后是乌麦克
Then Womack.
接着是迈克尔·科恩
Michael Kern.
佐伊的文章毁了他的机会
It was Zoe's article that ruined his chances.
你认识她  你去过她家附近
You knew her. You were in her neighborhood.
这不负责任  汤姆
This is irresponsible, Tom.
整个国家正受到恐怖主义的重大威胁
When the whole nation is in the middle of this major terror threat.
独裁者们用的也是这套逻辑
That's the same reasoning dictators use.
你让我想到凯特·鲍德温
You remind me a little bit of Kate Baldwin.
你失去了客观性
You've lost your objectivity.
你竟然提到她  真是有趣
Uh, it's funny you mention her.
凯特认为卢卡斯有所发现  我让她别管
Kate thought Lucas was onto something. I told her to let it go,
因为什么都没有  但其实有
that there wasn't anything there, but there was.
那事实在哪  事实  不是引言  事实
Well, where are the facts? Facts, not quotes. Facts.
你想看见事实
You wanna see a fact?
这就是事实
This is a fact.
我告诉你他疯了  这就是证据
I told you he was crazy, and there's the proof.
他的事实找错了  但他的方向是对的
He had the facts wrong, but he had the story right.
他看透了你
He saw through you.
什么方向  我是个心理变态
So what is the story? That I'm some sort of psychopath?
我是个杀人犯
That I'm a killer?
我从不相信你是杀人犯  现在也不信
Oh, I never believed you were a murderer, and I still don't.
但我越来越难以不去考虑这种可能性
But it's becoming harder not to entertain the thought.
那我要不要给你把枪  好让你也来射杀我
Well, should I get you a gun, so you can shoot me, too?
他说中了你的灵魂
He was right about your soul.
说中了你骨子里的东西
What's in your bones.
你残酷无情  腐化不堪
That you're ruthless. You're corrupt.
阻拦你的东西  你一律摧毁
You destroy whatever's in your path.
有哪个总统不符合你这番描述
Name me a president you wouldn't describe in exactly the same way.
我们都残酷无情  都摧毁事物
We're all ruthless. We all destroy.
至于腐败  那就是视角问题了
But corruption? That's a matter of perspective.
不
No.
是法律问题
It's a matter of law.
行了  你现在有点困惑  汤姆
All right, you seem a little confused here, Tom.
上一秒还在谈我的灵魂
One moment you're talking about my soul,
下一秒就跳到法律
and the next moment you want to get legal.
我们今天至少说明白点什么  好吗
Let's at least achieve some clarity here today, shall we?
你想要事实真相吗
You want the real story?
佐伊·巴恩斯
Zoe Barnes?
对  我们在工作上有交集
Yes, we knew each other. Professionally.
我们互相帮忙
I scratched her back and she scratched mine.
是你把这些印出来的
And you printed all of it.
你是她教育法案时的线人
You were her source for the education bill.
-还有迈克尔·科恩  -你拆他台
- And Michael Kern. - You sabotaged him.
问问你自己  我为什么要做这些事
Okay, ask yourself why I would have done all those things.
因为那个教育法案太糟糕了
Because the education bill was a disaster,
我必须得帮总统跳出泥潭
and I had to move the president off of it.
因为迈克尔·科恩是个糟糕的国务卿人选
Because Michael Kern was a terrible choice for Secretary of State.
我们应该选个更好的  也确实选出来了  凯茜
We could do better, and we did, with Cathy.
我是在帮沃克
I was trying to help Walker.
我是在引导一位软弱的总统走上正途
I was trying to steer a weak president in the right direction.
你要是想发表这一段  尽管发表好了
Now, you want to print that story, you go right ahead.
但是其余的部分都是胡扯
But the rest of it is just nonsense.
你没和雷蒙德·塔斯克达成任何协议
You didn't make any deals with Raymond Tusk?
-绝对没有  -那你为什么赦免他
- Absolutely not. - Then why did you pardon him?
和我赦免了沃克是一个原因
Same reason I pardoned Walker.
因为这个国家必须向前看
Because the country had to move on.
弹劾的事不是你策划的
You didn't orchestrate his impeachment?
我为什么会想着弹劾一位
Why would I want to impeach a president
我拼命辅佐的总统呢
I was working so hard to help?
你还在这儿  他却不在了
You're still here. He's not.
我曾尽力阻止他伤害自己
I was trying to save him from himself.
很不幸  我失败了
Unfortunately, I failed.
-你相信自己的直觉吗  汤姆  -一直都信
- Do you trust your instincts, Tom? - I always have.
那你看着我的眼睛
Then look me in the eye.
我告诉你的是真相
I've told you the truth.
你说的话
What you said...
算公开声明吗
is it on the record now?
你相信我吗
Do you believe me?
一点都不信
Not for a second.
那就不算  一个字都不算
Then, no. Not a word.
我们会给你几个小时准备正式回应
We'll give you a few hours if you want to make an official comment.
我要走了
I'm ready to go now.
如果他们放了那位父亲  你就是个英雄
If they release the father, you're a hero.
还不够  我不知道我们该怎么处理这篇报道
It's not enough. I don't know how we survive this story.
我的脑子里全是事儿  一遍遍翻来覆去
My mind keeps racing, over and over and over again.
可以处理得更好的事
What we could've done differently.
本可以掩盖的线索
How we could've covered our tracks.
应该搞好的关系
The people we should've kept closer...
我害怕  克莱尔
I'm frightened, Claire.
如果我们不能防止损失
If we can't stop the damage,
就必须止损  弗兰西斯
we have to control it, Francis.
办法是有的  一直都有
There is a solution. There always is.
稍等
Hold on.
他们打来了  先生
They're on, sir.
我们刚收到消息
We just got word.
-他们打来了  -是的  我也刚刚得知
- They've called in. - Yes, I was just told.
好吧  先处理这件事  一件一件来吧
All right, this first. One thing at a time.
-连好了吗  - 是的  夫人
- The link is up? - Yes, ma'am.
我们已经定位到了那栋建筑
We've located the building.
符合卡洛琳·米勒的描述
Matches the description from Caroline Miller
也符合到她们释放地点的驾车时间
and the drive time from where they were found.
我们确定他们在那儿吗
Are we certain that they're there?
不  先生  但我们有一队人马在路上了
No, sir, but we have a team en route.
看看一会儿通话是什么情况
Let's see how the phone call goes,
然后我们再决定是否行动
and then we'll decide if we're gonna move.
开始连线了
The line is open.
连吧
Go ahead.
-我是总统  -艾哈迈德呢
- This is the president. - Where's Ahmadi?
一会儿让他视频连线
We're about to connect him via video,
这样你就知道他可以自由发言
so you know that he's speaking freely.
但是连线之前  记住
But before we do, be aware
如果你把这段通话中的任何部分泄露给媒体
that if you release any of this call to the media,
我们讨论过的所有提议都会作废
anything we discuss will be off the table.
让他连线
Put him on.
真主保佑
Assalam-alaikum.
真主也保佑你
Walaikum-assalam.
我知道你们在试图营救我
I know you are trying to free me.
说英语
English.
听我说
Listen to me.
你们已经完成了使命
You've already done your duty.
你们已经引起了世界的注意
You have made the world pay attention.
但是美国政府不会释放我的
But the U.S. Government, they will not free me.
如果你们伤害了这个人
And if you harm this man,
他们会让穆斯林流更多的血
they'll bring more bloodshed on Muslims.
放了他吧
Let him go.
他们向我保证只以绑架罪起诉你们
They have promised me they will only charge you for kidnapping...
而不是恐怖袭击
not as terrorists.
你是受迫这么说的吗
Are they forcing you to say this?
不是
No.
你在看谁
Who are you looking to?
关掉
Off.
他们挂了
They've hung up.
他刚刚说了什么
What did he just say?
你刚才说的是什么
What did you say?
告诉我你说了什么
Tell me what you said.
我不是个叛徒
I'm not a traitor.
把他关在这儿
Keep him down here.
"把视频发布出去
"Release the video.
如果他们不放我回家  就杀了他们
If they don't send me home, kill them.
艾哈迈德与劫持者对话公布
如果他们抓到你  杀了他
If they find you, kill him.
确保你有证据..."  然后就断了
Make sure you have proof that I--" And then it goes black.
现在情况如何  我们并不清楚
Where that leaves us, we don't know right now.
白宫没有向媒体通报  也没有发布声明
The White House has not briefed the press or issued any statement--
我该怎么说
What do I say to this?
-我们什么都不说  -不能不回应
- We say nothing. - No, I can't say nothing,
外面有100多个记者准备破门而入
'cause I got 100 reporters that are about to break down that door.
在了解确切情况前
We are not going to expose ourselves
我们不能暴露自己
until we have something concrete to go on.
等那男的人头落地  还是到时也不说
Like the guy's head rolling? Or are you saying nothing then, too?
《先驱报》那篇文章呢
Or how about the Herald article?
等那发布了  你也准备什么都不说吗
When that comes out, are you gonna say nothing?
赛斯...
Seth...
我可以把我锁在这间屋子里
Look, I will lock myself up in here.
找个地缝钻进去
I'll bury my head in the sand.
但最终  面对这群人的还是我
But eventually, it's me that has to face these people.
我不能像你一样藏起来
All right, I can't hide the way that you--
闭嘴  闭嘴
Stop. Stop!
控制好你自己
Keep your shit together.
行吗
Okay?
吃点东西  闭上眼睛歇会
Eat some food. Rest your eyes for a little bit.
等我有进一步消息了联系你
I'll let you know when I know more.
-先生...  -现在不行
- Oh, sir, a-- - Not now.
-你把他带到这儿来了  -我自己来的
- You brought him here? - I brought myself.
事情很严重  道格
It's serious, Doug.
准备
Ready.
上  上  上
Go, go, go!
上  上  上  上
Go, go, go, go!
上  上  上
Go! Go! Go!
-安全  -安全
- Clear. - Clear.
安全
Clear.
-屋子是空的  -周围安全
- It's empty. - All clear.
-是空的  先生  -已确认周围安全
- It's empty, sir. - Confirmed. All clear.
-弗兰西斯他们找到了...  -没有
- -Francis, did they find-- - No.
我以为艾哈迈德会...
I thought Ahmadi was going to...
已经到这一步了
No, we are where we are.
我们知道他是个风险
We knew it was a risk.
-你还好吗  -我没事
- You okay? - Yes, I'm fine.
我扶你上楼
Let's get you upstairs.
安德伍德夫妇踏入总统办公室的歪门邪道
...15分钟前由汤姆·汉默施密特发表
...by Tom Hammerschmidt, 15 minutes ago.
文中提到曾请总统做出评价
In the article, it says the President was asked to comment,
但遭到拒绝
but declined.
文中引用了包括前总统加勒特·沃克
Among those quoted are ex-President Garrett Walker,
众议员杰姬...
Congresswoman Jackie--
到现在你收到了多少电话
How many phone calls have you got so far?
至少30个
Uh, at least 30.
-你呢  -我已经懒得数了
- You? - Ah, I stopped counting.
我们该去哪
Where should we go?
给我个惊喜吧
Surprise me.
不  我们什么都不说
No, we don't say anything.
让他在聚光灯下烧几天
We'll let him burn in the lights for a few days
看看情况如何
and see how this plays out.
然后在每个摇摆州放广告
And then we blanket every swing state with ads.
30秒  不放声音  只放标题
Thirty seconds, in silence. Just the headline.
让它沉入人们的脑子里
Let that sink into people's gray matter.
好的  回头聊
Okay. We'll talk soon.
过来  我想给你看个东西
Come here. I wanna show you something.
我还在生气
I'm still upset.
你不能假装什么都没发生过
You can't pretend that nothing's happened.
我不软弱
I am not weak.
我不该那么说  我知道你不
I shouldn't have said that. I know you're not.
我还知道点别的
And here's something else I know.
你就要成为下一位美国第一夫人了
You're gonna be the next First Lady of the United States.
好的  待在办公室
All right, stay in your office.
我待会打给你
I'll call you back in a bit.
来点降压药和阿司匹林吧
Some Prinivil and aspirin, please.
已经发出来了
It's out?
对
Yes.
麦卡伦找到了道格那儿
Doug's got Macallan with him, too.
他们在扩大他的项目  但不由他负责
They're expanding his program, but without him in charge.
我们在那头也不安全
So we're not safe there, either.
如果他...
Well, if he was...
如果是他掌管还好  但不是  所以
if he was there to manage it, but he's not, so...
不  我们不安全
No, we're not safe.
-要我叫萨克逊医生吗  -不必
- Should I call Dr. Saxon? - No, it's not necessary.
-非常感谢  先这样吧  -好的  先生
- Thank you very much. That'll be all. - Yes, sir.
还有三周...
Three weeks...
就要大选了
then the election.
这没什么
It's nothing.
然后我们败选
And then we lose.
然后他们调查
And they investigate.
我们的一切...
And everything we...
一去不复返
Gone.
我觉得
I feel...
麻木
numb.
我也是
I do, too.
我们可以制造时间
We make time.
我们无法把一切逐个击退  弗兰西斯
We can't fight everything off one by one, Francis.
但如果我们让这件事
But if we make this...
为我们所用
we make it work for us.
制造混乱
Create chaos.
不只是混乱
More than chaos.
战争
War.
恐惧
Fear.
残忍
Brutal.
彻底的
Total.
我受够了试图赢取人心
I'm done trying to win over people's hearts.
我们来攻击人心吧
Let's attack their hearts.
我们可以利用恐惧
We can work with fear.
是的  没错
Yes, we can.
你应该换一套新西装
You should put on a fresh suit.
海军蓝
The navy blue.
对  就那件
Yes, the navy blue.
-麦卡伦呢  -我们让他回去了
- Where's Macallan? - We sent him home.
好  让他待着  我们回头处理
All right, tell him to stay put. We'll tackle that later.
让赛斯联系媒体  一小时后  椭圆办公室
Have Seth inform the networks. The Oval, one hour.
-需要他起草什么吗  -让汤姆来写
- Do you need him to draft something? - Tom will write it.
-他不在这里  -那把他找来
- He's not here. - Then get him here.
你划掉的最后一段是什么
What about the last part that you crossed out?
"哀悼不是恐惧  悲痛不是认输"
Uh, "To mourn is not to fear. To grieve is not to admit defeat."
这段应该保留
You should keep that in.
但那是假定他会死
But it presumes he's going to die.
他就是会死
He is going to die.
我们先和律师谈  然后你再和媒体谈
We talk to the lawyers first, then you can talk to the press.
今天已有几大金主退出了
I've got major funders pulling out already.
总统应该打电话安抚他们
The President should put in calls to set them at ease.
不  不打电话  竞选事宜搁置
No. No calls. The campaign's on hold.
那些资金丢了就丢了
We lose that money, so be it.
我们要稳住
We need to stabilize.
我觉得他该去掉哀悼和悲痛那一段
I don't think he should say the part about mourning and grief.
我也觉得  但耶茨说他们想保留
I agree, but Yates said they wanted it back in.
是真的吗
Is it true?
汉默施密特写的那些
What Hammerschmidt wrote?
-是真的吗  -不是
- Is it? - No.
这是你不再对我说谎之后
That's the first time you've lied to me...
第一次又对我说谎了
since you stopped lying to me.
美国同胞们  过去两年里
My fellow Americans, over the past two years,
特别是过去的几天  几小时里
certainly within the last several days and hours,
我都在自问  "做总统意味着什么
I have asked myself, "What does it mean to be President?
真正的领导什么样的"
What does true leadership look like?"
随着11月临近  你们很多人
It's a question many of you have asked yourselves
也在自问这个问题
as November approaches.
我正坐在这间办公室的这把椅子上
Right now, as I sit in this chair, in this office,
在这里  我那么多先辈
where so many of my predecessors
曾带领我们的国家走过动荡
have steered our nation through turbulent times...
我发现这份工作
I realize that this job
是在政治游戏和华丽言辞之上的
is one that transcends politics and rhetoric.
坐在这个位置的人  肩负着的
Entrusted to anyone who sits behind this desk
是远远更为基本的东西  我们民族的生存
is something far more elemental, the very survival of our nation.
而我作为你们的总统  必须直面眼前的风暴
And I, as your President, must confront the storm before us.
这风暴便是恐怖主义
That storm is terror.
它比任何飓风都要危险和不可预知
More dangerous and unpredictable than any hurricane.
它在国外威胁着我们
It has endangered us abroad.
在国内也一样
It has endangered us at home.
而现在  它让詹姆斯·米勒
And right now, it has placed James Miller
处于最危险的境地中
in the gravest of dangers.
我们曾尝试与劫持者沟通
We attempted to communicate with his captors.
我们曾希望争取一个和平方案
We hoped for a peaceful solution.
我们庆幸
We're relieved that
卡洛琳和梅莉莎·米勒现在平安无事
Caroline and Melissa Miller are safe and sound.
但恐怖分子是蛮不讲理的
But terror is blind to reason.
在放弃恐怖的机会面前
Given the opportunity to renounce terror,
尤瑟夫·艾哈迈德选择了鼓励恐怖
Yusuf Al Ahmadi chose to encourage it.
所以  很不幸
So, unfortunately,
我们现在要放弃讲理了
we must now move beyond reason.
我们必须以武力回应
We must respond with force.
因为我们无论如何也不会释放他
Because there is no scenario in which we will release him.
他会继续被美国羁押  直至死亡
He will remain in United States custody until his dying breath.
如果劫持者再次来电  我们不会回答
If the captors call again, we will not answer.
沟通的阶段已过  不论后果如何
The time for conversation is over, no matter the consequences.
不论詹姆斯·米勒最终是否被释放
Regardless of whether James Miller is released or not,
是否获救
rescued or not,
是否被杀
killed or not...
哈里发国都会被彻底摧毁
ICO will be destroyed.
我们开战了
We are at war.
这场战争所波及的范围  将远超此前
It will be a war more total than anything we have waged thus far
我们发动的任何一场反恐战争
in the fight against extremism.
战士会战死
Soldiers will die.
平民会伤亡
Civilians may die.
我们会遭受痛苦  我们会遇到磨难
There will be pain. There will be suffering.
我们会面对人性中最恐怖的一面
We will be confronted with the most horrific aspects of humanity.
我们会面对人性的丧失
We will confront the inhuman.
乃至邪恶本身
Evil itself.
但我们一定会取得胜利
But we will triumph.
这场战争  我们输不起
It is not a war we will lose.
如果詹姆斯·米勒惨遭不幸
And if the worst happens to James Miller...
我们必须铭记他
we must remember,
哀悼不是恐惧
To mourn is not to fear.
悲痛不是认输
To grieve is not to admit defeat.
上帝保佑美国
God bless America,
保佑所有热爱自由和民主的人们
and all of those who believe in freedom and democracy.
-有消息吗  -他们刚刚发了推特
- Any news? -They just posted on Twitter.
九点整  全网直播
9:00 sharp, live on the Internet.
我们来不及找到他们
We won't find them before that.
我们能拦截他们的视频吗
Do we have the capability to block the video?
我们能拦截几个网站
Well, we might be able to block some sites,
-但如果他们的镜像足够多  -不用拦截
- but if they have enough mirrors-- - Don't block anything.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
让全世界好好看看
The whole world should watch this.
我们也要看
And we should, too.
-你说"我们开战了"  -我想建立个联盟
- What you said, "We're at war..." - I want to build a coalition.
-更多空袭吗  -地面进攻  空袭
- More air strikes? - Ground, air...
我要全军进攻
The full force of our military.
你应该先咨询一下我的
Well, I wish you would have consulted first.
这么大规模的扩大行动
This type of escalation--
这不是扩大行动  凯茜  这是全面铲除
Not escalation, Cathy. Obliteration.
你是想以此回应那篇报道吗
This is your response to the article?
该做的就得做
We're doing what's necessary.
找到绑匪之后  就地正法
When you find them... you will kill them.
如果能活捉的话  我们也许能问出...
If we're able to apprehend alive, we may get--
我明白了  总统先生
I understand, Mr. President.
先生
Sir?
我想全身心投入  我能做到
I wanna be 100%. I can give you that.
但是会很不容易  因为我...
But it's gonna be a lot harder if I...
如果您需要我留在您身边  我会的
If you want me here by your side, I will be.
-但我更希望  -不
- But I'd prefer-- - No.
该怎么做就怎么做  完事了就回来
You do what you have to do. Be back when it's over.
我会的  谢谢  先生
I will. Thank you, sir.
你要不要进屋去
Do you want to come inside?
-孩子们在吗  -在
- The kids there? - Yeah.
-你不想让他们看...  -不
- You're not letting them watch... - No.
我禁止他们看
No, I forbade them to.
不过他们还得上学  他们还有朋友
Although, I mean, with school and... and their friends,
如果他们真的想看
it'll be impossible to prevent if...
我也是拦不住的
if they really wanna see it.
他们还好吗
They all right?
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我会好的
I will be.
我必须得好
I have to be.
这一家家的人
All these people in their houses...
马上就要看到可怕的镜头
about to see this awful thing...
然后这辈子都忘不掉
that they'll never be able to erase.
你丈夫去世的时候  你在吗
Were you there, when your husband died?
你在房间里吗
In the room?
不在
No.
你曾经亲眼看着别人死吗
Have you ever watched someone die?
我知道你今晚必须得回去
I know you gotta go back there tonight...
但是等你忙完
but when you're done...
不管忙到多晚
whenever that is...
都要来这里
you're staying here.
以哈里发国和尤瑟夫·艾哈迈德的名义
We do this in the name of the Islamic Caliphate,
以真主的名义  我们处决此人
in the name of Yusuf Al Ahmadi, in the name of God.
梅莉沙  我爱你  卡洛琳  我爱你
Melissa, I love you. Caroline, I love you.
亲爱的上帝  请照顾...
Please, dear God, look out--
请把声音关上
Turn off the sound.
就是这样
That's right.
我们不对恐怖低头
We don't submit to terror.
我们制造恐怖
We make the terror.